let questions = [
    {
    number: 1,
    
    question: " The number of items used by the dynamic array contents is its ",
    answer: "Logical size",
    options: [
      "Physical size",
      "Capacity",
      "Logical size",
      "Random size"
    ]
  },
    
  {
    number: 2,
    question: "Which of the following is the implementation of the ternary tree?",
    answer: " Ternary Heap",
    options: [
      "AVL Tree",
      "Ternary Heap",
      "Hash Table",
      "Dictionary"
    ]
  },

  {
    number: 3,
    question: " What is the time complexity for inserting/deleting at the beginning of the array?",
    answer: "O(n)",
    options: [
      "O(1)",
      "O(n)",
      "O(logn)",
      "O(nlogn)"
    ]
  },

  {
    number: 4,
    question: "The worst case complexity of deleting any arbitrary node value element from heap is",
    answer: "O(logn)",
    options: [
      " O(logn)",
      "O(n)",
      " O(nlogn)",
      " O(n2)"
    ]
  },

  {
    number: 5,
    question: "What is the number of edges present in a complete graph having n vertices?",
    answer:  "(n*(n-1))/2",
    options: [
      "(n*(n+1))/2",
      "(n*(n-1))/2",
      "n",
      "Information given is insufficient"
    ]
  },

  {
    number: 6,
    question: " Why we need to a binary tree which is height balanced?",
    answer: "to avoid formation of skew trees",
    options: [
      "to avoid formation of skew trees",
      "to save memory",
      "to attain faster memory access",
      "to simplify storing"
    ]
  },

  {
    number: 7,
    question: " A graph with all vertices having equal degree is known as a ",
    answer: "Regular Graph",
    options: [
      "Multi Graph",
      "Regular Graph",
      "Simple Graph",
      "Complete Graph"
    ]
  },

  {
    number: 8,
    question: "The topological sorting of any DAG can be done in ________ time.",
    answer: "linear",
    options: [
      "cubic",
      "quadratic",
      "linear",
      "logarithmic"
    ]
  },

  {
    number: 9,
    question: "Which of the following is a disadvantage of using separate chaining using linked lists?",
    answer: "It requires many pointers",
    options: [
      "It requires many pointers",
      "It requires linked lists",
      "It uses array",
      "It does not resolve collision"
    ]
  },

  {
    number: 10,
    question: " What is the time complexity of insert function in a hash table using a binary tree?",
    answer: "O(1)",
    options: [
      "O(1)",
      "O(n)",
      "O(log n)",
      "O(n log n)"
    ]
  },
];